pccasegear.com 2018-10-20

# Privacy Notice : PC Case Gear

**PC Case Gear Privacy Policy**

PC Case Gear Pty Ltd ABN 14 099 808 072 **** (referred to as **PCCG** , **we** , **us** or **our** ) has implemented this Privacy Policy to provide **you** with information about how we collect, hold and use Personal Information on the PCCG website (www.pccasegear.com.au) ( **Website** ) and generally. We are committed to the protection of your Personal Information in accordance with the Australian National Privacy Principles set out in the _Privacy Act 1988 (Cth)_. 

If you wish to make any inquiries regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact our Privacy Officer as specified in clause 10. 

We may, from time to time, review and update this Privacy Policy including, to take into account new laws, regulations and technology. All Personal Information held by us will be governed by our most recent Privacy Policy, posted on our Website.

**1.** **What is "Personal Information"?**

" **Personal Information** " is information or an opinion, whether true or not, and whether recorded in a material form or not, about an individual whose identity is apparent, or can reasonably be ascertained. Personal Information collected may include (but is not limited to) the following: 

(a) name, postal, billing, email and social media (e.g. Twitter and Facebook) addresses ;  
(b) contact details including telephone numbers (landline, mobile and fax); and  
(c) payment details. 

**2.** **When and why we collect Personal Information**

2.1 We collect your Personal Information to manage our ongoing relationship with you and perform functions and activities relating to our business as further described in clause 4. 

2.2 We may collect Personal Information such as your name, email contact details, billing and delivery addresses, and payment details __ when you: 

(a) create an account on our Website;  
(b) access and use our Website (see clause 3);  
(c) request information about us, our services or a product;  
(d) request technical support or warranty assistance;  
(e) provide feedback or make new product requests;  
(f) subscribe to our general newsletter;  
(g) fill in a form on our Website;  
(h) contact us by telephone, email, through social media such as Facebook, post or in person; or  
(i) submit a resume (whether unsolicited or not) when you apply for an employee position with us. 

**3.** **Information collected via our** **Website**

3.1 We will not collect any Personal Information about users of our Website except when they knowingly provide it or as otherwise described below. 

**_Click Stream Data_**

3.2 When you visit and browse our Website, our Website host may collect information for statistical, reporting and maintenance purposes. 

3.3 Subject to clause 6.4, the information collected by our Website host will not be used to identify you. The information may include: 

(a) the number of users visiting our Website and the number of pages viewed;  
(b) the date, time and duration of a visit;  
(c) the IP address of your computer; or  
(d) the path taken through our Website.  

3.4 Our Website host uses this information to administer and improve the performance of our Website. 

3.5 We use Google Analytics to help analyse how you use our Website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating is used to create reports about the use of the Website. Google will store this information. We will not (and will not allow any third party to) use Google Analytics to track or to collect any personally identifiable information of visitors to our Website. We will not associate any data gathered from this Website with any personally identifying information from any source as part of our use of Google Analytics. 

3.6 If you do not want your Website visit data reported by Google Analytics, you can install the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. For more details on installing and uninstalling the add-on, please visit the Google Analytics opt-out page at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. 

**_Cookies_**

3.7 Cookies are small text files that are transferred to a user's computer hard drive by a website for the purpose of storing information about a user's identity, browser type or website visiting patterns. Cookies may be either "persistent" or "session" cookies. A persistent cookie will be stored on the user's computer and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before then. A session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the internet browser is closed. 

3.8 If you access our Website, a cookie is downloaded onto your computer's hard drive when you first log on to our Website. Our Website uses session cookies but also persistent cookies for Google Analytics. __

3.9 You can adjust your internet browser to disable cookies, or you can delete cookies already stored on your computer, however we may not be able to provide you with all the service or functionality you require on our Website if you choose to do so. 

**4.** **How we use the Personal Information we collect about you**

4.1 We use the Personal Information we collect about you for our business functions and activities, which may include the following: 

(a) to communicate with you and provide you with information, products or services you have requested;  
(b) to manage and administer your account including in relation to all purchases, product tracking, deliveries, returns, exchanges and warranty claims;  
(c) to promote and market our services and the products sold on our Website to you;  
(d) to personalise and customise your experiences on our Website;  
(e) to help us research the needs of our customers, and to gain a better understanding of your needs and the needs of customers generally;  
(f) to conduct research for the purposes of improving our services, creating new services or updating the product lines on our Website;  
(g) if you have chosen to subscribe to our electronic general newsletter, to allow us to provide advertising material to you regarding us, our clients, and other business partners; and  
(h) if you submit a resume when you apply for an employee position with us but are unsuccessful, to retain your resume on file for a period of 2 months for later consideration if another position becomes available.  

4.2 We may collect and use your Personal Information for other purposes not listed above. If we do so, we will make it known to you at the time we collect or use your Personal Information . 

4.3 We will only collect and use your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

4.4 If you choose not to provide your Personal Information to us for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, we may not be able to undertake certain activities for you such as providing you with requested information, products or services. 

**5.** **To whom we disclose your Personal Information**

5.1 In order to carry out the above purposes, we may disclose your Personal Information to third parties that provide products and services to or through PCCG (including third party couriers), our suppliers, distributors, vendors, financial institutions, our professional advisors, and other parties to whom we are authorised or required by law to disclose information. 

5.2 We may also disclose your Personal Information to our Website host or software application providers in certain limited circumstances, for example when our Website experiences a technical problem or to ensure that it operates in an effective and secure manner. 

5.3 The nature of the Internet means that some of your Personal Information may be transferred, stored, processed or used overseas by us or by third party service providers. This may happen if we outsource certain activities overseas or if transactions, information, services or products have an overseas connection. You consent to the collection, use, storage, and processing of your Personal Information outside of Australia. 

5.4 In connection with our use of Google Analytics, Personal Information may be disclosed to an entity or entities overseas where Google's servers are located, where it will be stored solely for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. In these circumstances, you consent to the collection, use, storage and processing of your Personal Information in those countries. 

**6.** **Marketing**

6.1 You may choose to subscribe to our electronic general newsletter, which contains store news and information about new products, special offers and other promotional announcements, using the "Newsletter Preferences" functionality in your account or using the newsletter "Subscribe" functionality on our Website home page. We will email the general newsletter to your email address. 

6.2 If you have chosen to subscribe to our electronic general newsletter, we may use your Personal Information to provide you with marketing material about us, our services, or products that we think may be of interest to you. We do not disclose any personally identifiable information of our users to advertisers. 

6.3 You may opt-out of receiving our electronic general newsletter and marketing information from us at any time by: 

(a) clicking on the "Unsubscribe" link included in any general newsletter you receive from us;  
(b) using the "Newsletter Preferences" functionality in your account; or  
(c) contacting our Privacy Officer in any of the ways specified in clause 10.  

6.4 Unless otherwise specified in this Privacy Policy, we or our Website host will not disclose any of your Personal Information to any other organisation unless the disclosure is required by law or is otherwise permitted by the National Privacy Principles. 

**7.** **Finding out what Personal Information we hold about you**

7.1 You are entitled to access Personal Information that we hold about you. If you request access to your Personal Information, we will grant your request unless providing you with access would unreasonably impact upon the privacy of others or is not otherwise permitted under the Australian National Privacy Principles. If we refuse your request to access your Personal Information, we will provide you with reasons for the refusal. 

7.2 A request for access can be made by contacting our Privacy Officer specified in clause 10. 

**8.** **Updating, storage and security of Personal Information held by us**

8.1 We aim to keep your Personal Information secure and up to date. Any Personal Information that is collected via our Website or which is held on our computer systems is protected by safeguards including physical, technical (eg firewalls, SSL encryptions etc) and procedural methods. 

8.2 Personal Information that is held by us in hard copy is stored securely on our premises and is only disclosed or used for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. 

8.3 You can update your contact and Personal Information at any time on the Website through the "Account Information" functionality in your account. If we find that we have no further need for your Personal Information we may remove it from our systems and destroy all record of it. We welcome notification from you of any changes to your details so as to keep our records up to date. 

8.4 In relation to resumes (whether unsolicited or not) we have on file, we will destroy them when the retention period of 2 months expires. 

**9.** **International Use and your Personal Information**

We make no representation or warranty that your Personal Information will be collected, held and used by us other than in accordance with Australian National Privacy Principles set out in the _Privacy Act 1988 (Cth)_. If you choose to access the Website from locations outside of Australia, you do so at your own risk and such access will be subject to the laws of Australia. 

**10.** **What to do if you have a question, problem or complaint about our use of your Personal Information or this Privacy Policy**

If you feel that your privacy has not been respected or that we have conducted ourselves inconsistently with this Privacy Policy in respect of your Personal Information, or for any other queries or communication in relation to this Privacy Policy, please contact our Privacy Officer by emailing privacyofficer@pccasegear.com 

Last updated: _[19/09/13]_
